This isn't a chatbot. It's a worker. You point simplicio-loop at a body of work — and it runs the whole job on its own.
这不是聊天机器人，而是一名工人。把 simplicio-loop 指向一批工作，它就会独立跑完整个任务。
Issues, CI failures, Jira boards — queues that never empty. And every pass burns more tokens. What if one command drained all of it, cheaply?
Issues、CI 失败、Jira 看板——永远清不完的队列，而每一轮都在烧更多的 token。如果一条命令就能廉价地清空它们呢？
First, pre-flight. A hard cost kill-switch, source auth, and a twenty-four-seven watcher — all green before a single line of code.
先做预检：硬性成本熔断、来源鉴权、7×24 守护进程——在写下第一行代码前全部亮绿。
It discovers fifty issues, dedups them, builds a dependency graph, and auto-scales a fleet of fourteen agents to your machine.
它发现五十个 issue，去重，构建依赖图，并根据你的机器自动扩展出十四个智能体。
Each item runs the full cycle: read the body and acceptance criteria, orient the code, plan, apply the edit mechanically, then run it. Because it has to work — not just compile.
每个条目都跑完整循环：读正文与验收标准，定位代码，规划，机械地应用改动，然后真正运行。因为它必须能用，而不只是能编译。
Quality gates fire: the acceptance-criteria check, three adversarial reviewers refuting in parallel. And a fail-closed safety gate blocks force-push and secrets before they ever run.
质量闸门启动：验收标准检查、三个对抗式审查者并行反驳。还有一个失败即关闭的安全闸门，在 force-push 和密钥运行前就拦住它们。
Token economy is relentless. An eight-hundred-seventy-line file collapses to sixty-five signatures — ninety-three percent saved. Output is clamped and cached. Watch the live dashboard: up to ninety-six percent fewer tokens.
token 经济毫不留情。八百七十行的文件被压成六十五行签名——节省百分之九十三。输出被裁剪并缓存。看实时仪表盘：最多减少百分之九十六的 token。
The loop never lies. The done-promise only fires with real proof — a passing test, a merged PR. A stall detector switches strategy instead of spinning. Never a false done.
循环从不说谎。完成承诺只有在拿到真实证据——测试通过、PR 合并——时才会触发。停滞检测器会切换策略而非空转。绝不会出现虚假的完成。
Ask for a demo video and it makes one. web_verify captures the screens, hyperframes renders a deterministic M-P-4, attached straight to the pull request as proof.
要一段演示视频，它就做一段。web_verify 截取画面，hyperframes 渲染出确定性的 MP4，直接作为证据附到 PR 上。
Eleven runtimes, one protocol — Claude, Codex, Copilot, Cursor, Gemini, Hermes and more. Same gates, same safety. Only the speed differs.
十一种运行时，一套协议——Claude、Codex、Copilot、Cursor、Gemini、Hermes 等等。相同的闸门，相同的安全。只有速度不同。
It merges, closes, and goes idle — then wakes the moment new work arrives. Twenty-four seven.
它合并、关闭、进入空闲——一旦有新工作就立刻唤醒。全天候 7×24。
Pip install simplicio-loop. One command installs everything. M-I-T, open, and waiting on GitHub. Join us.
pip install simplicio-loop。一条命令装好一切。MIT 开源，就在 GitHub 等你。加入我们。